Guide to the Papers of Mordecai Sheftall (1735-1797), undated, 1761-1867, 1873, 1932, 1941 (bulk 1777-1778) *P-12
American Jewish Historical Society, Newton Centre, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup II: American Revolutionary and Continental Troop Commissarial Work and Provision Return Records, undated, 1777-1779, 1782-1783
  - Series II: Commissarial Records - Army, undated, 1777-1778
    - Subseries XVII: Provision Returns for the Sick and Hospital, undated, 1778
      - (Binder 11)
        - Provision Return for Sick Belonging to the 4th Battalion Signed by A. Alexander [?] of the 2nd Battalion for Twelve Men and Two Women, 12/18/1778 (Item 258)
        - Provision Return for the Hospital and the 4th Battalion for One Woman and Five Children and Two Nurses of the Hospital, 12/18/1778 (Item 259)
    - Subseries XVIII: Provision Returns for the Wagoners, Georgia and Georgia and South Carolina, undated, 1778
      The last two Subseries of this Subgroup contain Provision Returns for the Wagoners or as they are called within the collection,Wagoners. In regards to Subseries XVIII, the returns are signed to either the Wagoners of Georgia itself, or to the Wagoners of both Georgia and South Carolina combined. Subseries XIX holds Provision Returns for the Wagoners of South Carolina only.
      This Subseries contains one-hundred and seventy-four Provision Returns. Names and signatures among this Subseries are: John Wandin, Will Robinson, Joseph Carr, Shadrack Wright, John Leduc, Robert Harrison, James Mitchelson, William Matthews, William Damant, Peter Damant, William Dell, John Sutcliffe, Patrick Stikes, Peter Horn, Joseph Carr, James McCallion, John Burgess, James Cheery, and George Young. The majority of Provision Returns are signed by James Mitchelson, the Conductor of Wagons.
      - (Binder 11)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin [Fragment], undated (Item 1)
        - Provision Return for the [Wagoners] Signed by Will Robinson, [Illegible], undated (Item 2)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Joseph Carr for Two Wagoners, undated (Item 3)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Shadrack Wright, undated (Item 4)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of Georgia and South Carolina Signed by John Leduc for the Georgia and South Carolina Brigades [Torn], undated (Item 5)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc [Fragment], undated (Item 6)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Sheftall Sheftall to Robert Harrison, Conductor of Wagons from 12/15/1777-03/09/1778, 03/24/1778 (Item 7)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wives and Children [Fragment], 1778 (Item 8)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 3rd Battalion Signed by James [McCallion] for Two Men, 02/10/1778 (Item 9)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 2nd Regiment Signed by William Matthews, 02/11/1778 (Item 10)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners 2nd and 3rd Regiment Signed by Robert Harrison for Twelve Wagoners and Five Women, 02/13/1778 (Item 11)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by William Damant for Two Wagoners and One Woman, 02/13/1778 (Item 12)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by William Damant for the Robert Harrison and John Whitman, 02/13/1778 (Item 13)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Peter Taarling to [Robert] Harrison, 02/14/1778 (Item 14)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners for the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd Battalions Signed by Robert Harrison, 02/17/[1778] (Item 15)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for John Whitman and Robert Harrison, 02/19/1778 (Item 16)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison, 02/20/1778 (Item 17)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for Thirteen Wagoners and Six Women, 02/20/1778 (Item 18)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd Battalions Signed by Robert Harrison for Wagoners and Wives, 02/24/1778 (Item 19)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, 02/24/1778 (Item 20)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st and 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison for Wagoners and Wives, 02/28/1778 (Item 21)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st and 3rd Battalions Signed by Robert Harrison, 03/[?]/1778 (Item 22)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, 03/03/1778 (Item 23)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for Six Wagons, 03/09/1778-03/24/1778 (Item 24)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison, 03/09/1778 (Item 25)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st and 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, 03/12/1778 (Item 26)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 3rd Battalion signed by William Dell Stationed at Cape Harrison, 03/14/1778 (04/13/1778) (Item 27)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners for the 1st and 3rd Battalions Signed by Robert Harrison for Nine Wives, 03/15/1778 (Item 28)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for One Wagoneer, 03/16/1778 (Item 29)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for Eight Wagoners, 03/16/1778 (Item 30)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison for [Seven or Eight] Wagoners, 03/20/1778 (Item 31)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Farquharson, and John Sutcliffe for Robert Harrison, Multiple Dates from 12/15/1777-03/09/1778, 03/21/1778 (Item 32)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st and 3rd Battalions Signed by Robert Harrison for Molasses for Nine Wagons, 03/23/1778 (Item 33)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 3rd Regiment Signed by Robert Harrison, 03/24?/1778 (Item 34)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st and 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, 03/28/1778 (Item 35)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, 03/28/1778 (Item 36)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, Conductor of Wagons, 03/30/1778 (Item 37)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st and 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, 04/01/1778 (Item 38)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, 04/04?/1778 (Item 39)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st and 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Harrison, 04/04/1778 (Item 40)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for Two Wagoners, 04/07?/1778 (Item 41)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison, 04/18/1778 (Item 42)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoneer Signed by John Sutcliffe for Three Wagoners, 04/22/1778 (Item 43)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for Two Men, 04/24?/1778 (Item 44)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 3rd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright, 05/08/1778 (Item 45)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd Battalions Signed by Robert Harrison for Fifteen Wagoners, 05/13/1778 (Item 46)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for Three Wagoners, 05/13/1778-03/15/1778 (Item 47)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for Patrick Stikes, Wagoners, 05/15/1778 (Item 48)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for Ten Wagoners of Col. Elbert's Brigade, 05/16/1778-05/10/1778 (Item 49)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Eight Wagoners Going to Fort Howe, 05/17/1778 (Item 50)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Peter Horn for Sixteen Wagoners, 05/18/1778 (Item 51)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st, 2nd and 3rd Battalions Signed by Robert Harrison for Seventeen Wagoneer, 05/19/1778 (Item 52)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for One Wagoneer, 05/20/1778 (Item 53)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson and John Farquharson to Robert Harrison, 05/20/1778 (Item 54)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for Seventeen Wagoners Belonging to Col. Elbert's Brigade, 05/22/1778-05/24/1778 (Item 55)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd Battalions Signed by Robert Harrison for Twenty-two Wagoners, 05/23/1778 (Item 56)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Joseph Carr for Sixteen Wagoners, 05/26/1778 (Item 57)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Shadrack Wright for Robert Harrison, 05/26/1778 (Item 58)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Shadrack Wright for Robert Harrison, 05/28/1778 (Item 59)
      - (Binder 9)
        - Provision Return for the Artillery and Waggoners Signed by Charles Noel Romand De Lisle for Capt. Fitzpatrick [Provision Return in Artificers], 05/28/1778 (Item 71 [60])
      - (Binder 11)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James McCallion for Twelve Wagoners, 05/31/1778 (Item 61)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Joseph Carr, 05/31/1778 (Item 62)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson, 06/[?]/[1778] (Item 63)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Shadrack Wright for Robert Harrison, 06/?/[1778] (Item 64)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Rum, 06/[?]/1778 (Item 65)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Three Wagoners, 06/03/1778 (Item 66)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Fourteen Wagoners, 06/06/1778 (Item 67)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Three [Days], 06/06/1778 (Item 68)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Thirteen Wagoners, 06/06/1778 (Item 69)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Burgess for Sixteen Wagoners, 06/08/1778 (Item 70)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Shadrack Wright for Mr. Morris, 06/10/1778 (Item 71)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for [Thirteen] Wagoners, 06/12/1778 (Item 72)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Thirteen Wagoners, 06/13?/1778 (Item 73)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Thirteen Wagoners, 06/15?/1778 (Item 74)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Thirteen Wagoners, 06/15/1778 (Item 75)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Tallow, 06/18/1778 (Item 76)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Fourteen Wagons, 06/18/1778 (Item 77)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Cherry for Eleven Men, 06/19/1778 (Item 78)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the Artillery Signed by James Cherry for Fifty-one Pounds of Raw Tallow, 06/19/1778 (Item 79)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Three Wagoners, 06/19/1/778 (Item 80)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the Artillery Signed by George Young for the Wagoners, Drivers, and One Conductor, 06/21/1778 (Item 81)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Fourteen Wagoners, 06/22/[1778] (Item 82)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Peter Taarling, John Leduc and James Mitchelson for Twelve Wagoners, 06/25/1778 (Item 83)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the Artillery Signed by George Young for Eleven Men of the Artillery, 06/29/1778 (Item 84)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for James Mitchelson for Wagoners of the [First?] Brigade, 06/29/1778 (Item 85)
        - Provision Return Signed by Peter Taarling for One Pint of Rum for One Waggoner and One [Illegible], 06/29/1778 (Item 86)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Mitchelson for Wagoners of the First Brigade, 06/30/1778 (Item 87)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for James Mitchelson) for Six Wagoners, 07/01/1778 (Item 88)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by [Torn] for Rum, 07/02/[1778] (Item 89)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners and Drivers of the Artillery Signed by George Young for James Cherry and Twelve Men, 07/02/1778 (Item 90)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by [Torn] and Received of Sheftall Sheftall One New Hide, "It being to cover a [Waggon] Carrying Medicines [torn] of the sick at Sunbury", 07/02/1778; WPA_E-0058; Indexed #067 (Item 91)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners and Drivers of the Artillery Signed by George Young for Fifteen Men, 07/04/1778 (Item 92)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for Twelve Rations, [07]/04/1778-[07]/05/1778 (Item 93)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for Twelve Rations, 07/06/1778-07/07/1778 (Item 94)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for Twelve Rations at Camp Fort Tonyn, 07/08/1778 (Item 95)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for Twelve Rations, 07/09/1778-07/10/1778 (Item 96)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Peter Taarling for Rum, 07/11/1778 (Item 97)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Robert Harrison for Fourteen Wagoners, 07/11/1778 (Item 98)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for Twelve Rations at Camp Fort Tonyn, 07/11/1778-07/12/1778 (Item 99)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Unsigned at Fort Tonyn Received Seventeen Gills of Rum, 07/13/1778 (Item 100)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for Three Rations, 07/13/1778 (Item 101)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Cherry for Twelve Men, 07/14/1778 (Item 102)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for the 2nd Brigade, 07/15/1778 (Item 103)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc, 07/15/1778 (Item 104)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the Artillery Signed by John Leduc, 07/15/1778 (Item 105)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc, 07/16/1778 (Item 106)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of Georgia and South Carolina Signed by John LeDuc for the Georgia and South Carolina Brigades, 07/16/1778 (Item 107)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoner Signed by Will Robinson for [Illegible], 07/17/1778 (Item 108)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the Artillery Brigade Signed by John Leduc, 07/17/1778 (Item 109)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for Fifteen Rations for One Day, 07/18/1778 (Item 110)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for the Artillery Wagons, 07/18/1778 (Item 111)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Will Robinson for Three [Illegible], 07/19/1778 (Item 112)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc (Two Returns), 07/19/[1778] (Item 113)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for Provisions at Reads Bluff (Three Returns), 07/19/1778 (Item 114)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for Seventeen Rations, 07/20/1778 (Item 115)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the Artillery Signed by John Leduc, 07/20/1778 (Item 116)
        - Provision Return for the Georgia and South Carolina Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for Wagoners, 07/20/1778 (Item 117)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the Artillery Signed by John Leduc for One Wagon Master, Ten Wagoners, and Four Soldiers, 07/21/1778 (Item 118)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for Sixteen Rations, 07/21/1778 (Item 119)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for the Artillery Wagons, 07/22/1778 (Item 120)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners of the Artillery Signed by John Leduc for One Wagon Master, Eight Wagoners, and Fourteen Soldiers, 07/22/1778 (Item 121)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for George McIntosh and Sixteen Wagoners, 07/22/1778 (Item 122)
        - Provision Return for the Georgia and South Carolina Wagoners Signed by John LeDuc for George McIntosh, 07/22/1778 (Item 123)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc for McIntosh for Fifteen Wagoners, Five Women and Illegible, 07/23/1778-07/24/1778 (Item 124)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Seven Wagoners, 07/25/1778 (Item 125)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by Shadrack Wright for Five Wagoners, 07/27/1778 (Item 126)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wardin for Two Days, 07/29/1778 (Item 127)
        - Provision Return for Wagoners Signed by John Wardin for Nine Wagoners, 07/31/1778 (Item 128)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Leduc at Fort McIntosh, 07/25/1778-07/26/1778 (Item 129)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for Two Wagoners, 08/03/1778 (Item 130)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for Twelve Wagoners, 08/03/1778 (Item 131)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin, 08/05/1778 (Item 132)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin, 08/07/1778 (Item 133)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin, 08/17/1778 (Item 134)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Twelve Wagoners, 08/19/1778 (Item 135)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Seven Wagoners, 08/26/1778 (Item 136)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson Eleven Wagoners, 08/26/1778 (Item 137)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Eleven Wagoners, 08/28/1778 (Item 138)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Ten Wagoners, 08/28/1778 (Item 139)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson, 09/01/[1778]-09/03/[1778] (Item 140)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wardin for Twelve Wagoners, 09/04/1778 (Item 141)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoners, Wives and Children, 09/04/[1778]-09/07/[1778] (Item 142)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson, 09/06/1778-09/11/1778 (Item 143)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoneer's Wives and Three Children, 09/08/1778-09/14/1778 (Item 144)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Eight Wagoners, 09/12/1778-09/14/1778 (Item 145)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Eight Wagoners, Two Women, and Three Children, 09/14/1778-09/19/1778 (Item 146)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for Five Wagoners, 09/14/1778 (Item 147)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for four Wagoners, Three Women and Two Children, 09/18/1778 (Item 148)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Six Wagoners, 09/20/1778 (Item 149)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Seven Wagoners, 09/20/1778 (Item 150)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoner's Wives and Three Children, [09]/21/1778-09/23/1778 (Item 151)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoners Wives and Three Children, 09/25/[1778] (Item 152)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoners Wives and Three Children, 09/25/1778 (Item 153)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for Four Wagonners and One Woman, 09/28/1778 (Item 154)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for Two Women and Three Children, 09/28/1778 (Item 155)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Ten Wagoners, 09/30/[1778] (Item 156)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Seven Wagoners, 10/1778 (Item 157)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Seven Wagoners, 10/1778 (Item 158)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Eight Wagoners, 10/1778 (Item 159)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Ten Wagoners, 10/01/1778 (Item 160)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Nine Wagoners, 10/02/1778 (Item 161)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoners Wives and Three Children, 10/02/1778 (Item 162)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoner's Wives and Three Children, 10/02/1778-10/08/1778 (Item 163)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoner's Wives and Three Children, 10/05/1778 (Item 164)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoner's Wives and Three Children, 10/07/1778 (Item 165)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson and the Mark of Thomas Simoons for Seven Wagoners, 10/09/1778 (Item 166)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wives, 10/09/1778 (Item 167)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Eight Wagoners, 10/13/1778 (Item 168)
        - Provision Return for Wagoners Signed by John Wandin for Two Wives and Three Children, 10/13/1778 (Item 169)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoneer's Wives and Three Children, 10/16/1778 (Item 170)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoners and Three Children, 10/20/1778 (Item 171)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoners and Three Children, 10/20/1778 (Item 172)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for One Wagoneer's Wife, 10/21/1778 (Item 173)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Eight Wagoners, 10/22/1778 (Item 174)
        - Provision Return for the [Wagoners] Signed by James Mitchelson and Meredith Davis for One [Illegible], 10/24/1778 (Item 175)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoneer's Wives and Three Children, 10/26/1778 (Item 176)
        - Provision Return for the [Wagoners] Signed by James Mitchelson for W. Davis, 10/27/1778 (Item 177)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoners Wive's and Children, 10/27/1778 (Item 178)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Wagoners [Illegible], 10/27/1778 (Item 179)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Two Wagoneer's Wives and Three Children, 10/30/1778 (Item 180)
        - Provision Return for the Wagoners Signed by James Mitchelson for Five Wagoners, 10/30/1778 (Item 181)
    - Subseries XIX: Provision Returns for the Wagoners, South Carolina, undated, 1778